

EMILIE TØNNESSEN FRONTEND DEVELOPER

CONTACT



Emilie Henriette Kathenes Tønnessen



12th of January 1996



+47 99168210



emilie@tonnessen.com



www.emilietonnessen.n etlify.app



www.github.com/emilie tonnessen

ABOUT ME

I am a 26-year-old frontend developer with an eye for design and structure. I am meticulous and good at seeing what needs to be done.

I am a conscientious and responsible person with a positive attitude. I'm a cheerful girl who enjoys spreading the joy of life. I am passionate about creating a good environment where everyone is looked after, heard, and appreciated. I really enjoy working with others, but I also enjoy working independently.

I love learning new things and developing myself as a person and in my professional field. Constructive criticism and debate are always welcome as they help me improve as developer and person.

HTML

CSS

- Sass
- Material UI
- JSS
- Bootstrap

JavaScript

- React JS
- Next JS
- TypeScript
- Redux

Rackend

Sanity

TECHNICAL SKILLS

I am well versed in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. When I write in JavaScript, I usually use it together with TypeScript.

I am most experienced with React JS + TypeScript. I also have experience with Next JS as I wrote my final exam with that framework.

Otherwise, I have experience with Sass, Material UI, Framer Motion, Bootstrap, Redux, Sanity, Figma, Adobe XD, Git, and JSS.

I am used to working in an agile workflow with sprints, story points and burndown charts.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Apr. 2022 - present Berg-Hansen Reisebureau AS Oslo

Working as a Junior Frontend Developer to create a new booking solution for Berg-Hansen's self-service website. We use technology such as React JS,

TypeScript, Redux and Material UI.

Jun. 2021 – Mar. 2022 Hurtigruten Group AS Oslo

Worked as a Junior Frontend Developer at Hurtigruten on their Agent Portal. We used React JS, TypeScript, Redux, Material UI and JSS. My tasks consisted of maintaining the website, solve bugs, and implementing

new features.

2017 – 2018 Adecco Asker and Bærum

Kindergarten Substitute

2016 – 2017 **Maxbo** Vækerø

Extra help on lumber dept.

2016 Maxbo Vækerø

Timber Seller, 100%

2014 - 2015 **Monter** Risør

Extra help and seasonal staff on lumber dept.

2013 – 2014 Risør Steinsenter Risør

Seasonal staff

EDUCATION

2019 - 2021 Frontend Development

Noroff - School of Technology and Digital Media, Online

2016 - 2019 Privatist

Sonans Oslo

2012 - 2014 VGS ST Toppidrett Hest

Melsom VGS

2002 - 2012 Grunnskole

Risør barne- og ungdomsskole

COURSES

Advanced CSS and Sass (Udemy)

"The most advanced and modern CSS course on the internet: master flexbox, CSS Grid, responsive design, and so much more."

Unit Testing Jest (Udemy)

"Master unit testing with NodeJs, Typescript, Jest and React. Write top quality Typescript and NodeJs software with Jest"